<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Feedbacks>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-02-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Worst lending experience of my life. My point of contact provided incorrect information from the start. This led me to spend money on items such as appraisal, which cost not quite twice as much as any other appraisal company in the area, and termite inspection. After putting charges on credit I had no choice but to close the loan to pay off new debt. Oh yes, one of those payments they have not made yet and they have yet to explain why. Won't return my calls. Can you say hello lawyer... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I feel they made promises that they could not keep and made some mistakes that personally cost me around $2,000; I would have canceled the loan a few different times if my finances would have allowed it.&#13;
&#13;
I would not recommend this company to any of my friends...&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>27-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I had an awful experience with Reliance when refinancing my home.  I would not recommend them to anyone.  Among other issues, it is now 3 weeks after we closed and i am still waiting for the check that i was told that i would receive at closing!  Not weeks after closing,  DO NOT USE THIS COMPANY!!!!!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>07-07-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Slow.  It took over 2 months to close. 2nd financial disclosure had an increase in borrowing amount.  Servicer said the increase was due to taxes being under estimated when, in fact, it was an increase in points.  I thought my rate had been locked.&#13;
They did not want to use my attorney so I went with theirs.  Without notifying me, their attorney did not do the closing.  A notary came to the house in a t-shirt.  The notary said he could not give legal advice so if we had any legal questions about the documents, we were out of luck, despite paying $625 for an attorney.  Later, I learned their attorney was sanctioned by the NC State Bar in 2005 for conduct related to real estate closings... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>29-07-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
My experience with Reliance wasn't good at all. 1st off they ran 4 hard inquires on my credit that i did not authorize and i am in the process of pursuing potential legal action . 2nd my rep corey scheduled an appraisal that took 6 weeks to get back and he nothing was done to speed that process up. 2nd we started this processs in sept and its jan of the next year almost and still not closed and i am still getting request from the loan processor. Its absolutely ridiculous! 3rd it took so long for them to close that the rate they offered me 3.75 went up to 4.6 and i wasn't even notified until i got documentation from Reliance. They did not lock me in to the initial rate like they should have. 3rd i decided not to use them for the refi because of all the errors and mistakes that were made by them. I'm going to file a Better Business Bureau complaint as well as other complaints about my experience, do not use them... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>26-06-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Nothing was as originally stated.  My closing costs were much higher than I was told in the beginning and I didn't get the money back that I was told I would.  When I complained I was told they were only estimates.  Even my appraisal ended up being $200 more.&#13;
&#13;
I was given a long list of painting &amp; work that had to be done before I could get FHA approval.  3 days after I paid to have it all done they switched me over to conventional.  &#13;
&#13;
I would not recommend them to a friend.  When all the red flags went up throughout the process I kept going because I was so far in and didn't want to start over with someone else.  Big mistake... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>23-01-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
We requested offers from three lenders.  This bank was the only one that wouldn't send us a tentative offer to review prior to their sales pitch.  It showed us that they really wanted to get us on the phone and give the hard sale.  For this reason I would not recommend them.  If their proposal didn't speak for its self without the sales pitch then I doubt it would have been a mutually beneficial deal. ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>06-02-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I can't say enough about Adam and Pac Ben. Talk about going the extra mile!!!  Holy Wow! Night and day difference from anyone else I considered and spoke with. Adam spent SOOOOOO much time, INCLUDING WEEKENDS, taking my questions, some of which I'm pretty sure were stupid, but he always took the time to walk me through and explain things very thoroughly. He also has a wonderfully calm yet passionate, knowledgeable yet approachable, and charming demeanor that made my mortgage  experience   so much better than I could have remotely expected. Made what could easily be unpleasant more than palatable. &#13;
&#13;
And above all, they made sure I was getting the BEST POSSIBLE DEAL for my scenario, which took some real work (no one provided a better rate, and you moght expect that "you get what you pay for", but not here, not at all 5 star service at the best rate you can get, why go anywhere else? 100% going back to Adam/Pac Ben when the time comes again, and I know it will. &#13;
&#13;
BUT HONESTLY, DO NOT GO TO ANYONE ELSE. &#13;
&#13;
Thanks Adaml!&#13;
... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>05-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I can't say enough about Adam, Bill and Pac Ben. Talk about going the extra mile!!!  Holy Wow! Night and day difference from anyone else I considered and spoke with. Adam spent SOOOOOO much time, INCLUDING WEEKENDS, taking my questions, some of which I'm pretty sure were stupid, but he always took the time to walk me through and explain things very thoroughly. He also has a wonderfully calm yet passionate, knowledgeable yet approachable, and charming demeanor that made my mortgage  experience   so much better than I could have remotely expected. Made what could easily be unpleasant more than palatable. &#13;
&#13;
And above all, they made sure I was getting the BEST POSSIBLE DEAL for my scenario, which took some real work (no one provided a better rate, and you moght expect that "you get what you pay for", but not here, not at all 5 star service at the best rate you can get, why go anywhere else? 100% going back to Adam/Pac Ben when the time comes again, and I know it will. &#13;
&#13;
BUT HONESTLY, DO NOT GO TO ANYONE ELSE. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Thanks Adam and Bill!&#13;
... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>21-02-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Jason, June and the team did an amazing job. This was our third refinance with Pacific Beneficial and it closed in 2 weeks! We were more than impressed and would recommend them to anyone looking for a mortgage or refi in CA. Our loan had no cost and the appraisal was waived. Thanks again you guys!!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-11-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Jason, June and the team did an amazing job. This was our third refinance with Pacific Beneficial and it closed in 2 weeks! We were more than impressed and would recommend them to anyone looking for a mortgage or refi in CA. Our loan had no cost and the appraisal was waived. Thanks again you guys!!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>29-10-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Jason, June and the team did an amazing job. This was our third refinance with Pacific Beneficial and it closed in 2 weeks! We were more than impressed and would recommend them to anyone looking for a mortgage or refi in CA. Our loan had no cost and the appraisal was waived. Thanks again you guys!!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>11-06-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Shawn is organized, quick to respond, transparent, and personable. He was very patient with me - a first-time home buyer - in answering all of my questions and explaining processes to me. He made the home buying process as painless as possible. Would recommend to anyone!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>09-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
The entire process was extremely stressful, due to circumstances beyond our control.  Michele Alves, Adam Carrion and Bill James worked diligently to make sure our refinance was able to be completed.  Bill James was so helpful in getting through the "messy issues" we had.  He was extremely patient with my questions and I always felt that I was the only client Pacific Beneficial had.  You do not see customer service of such a high caliber very often these days, and it was extremely refreshing.  I would, without hesitation, recommend Pacific Beneficial Mortgage Company to anyone... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>15-09-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Adam and his team are absolutely wonderful!  I had several "issues" with my refinance that caused additional problems, but Adam and Bill worked so hard to help us get in a better position. I would, with absolutely no reservation, recommend Adam.  Both Adam and Bill were so patient with my questions and concerns and helped the refinance go as smoothly as possible.  I was extremely fortunate in finding Adam and Bill... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>09-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Adam Carrion was hands down the best! Always there to answer any questions or let us know next steps and status at anytime of the day or night. Process was very simple, I provided a few items and Adam and his team handled everything else. It was the best experience you can have while refinancing. I would definitely recommend and will do business again in the future! Fast, simple and painless. Thank you!... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>23-01-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Outstanding! My wife and I have had many previous loans in the past. This by far was one of our best experiences. Alex Jocovic was wonderful, from first phone call to the end, he was with us every step of the way, not just sales. Our situation was complicated, with a 1031 exchange involved from a prior rental, a new home and all its confusion, sill Alex Jocovic was with us every day. We received status of the progress almost daily. So many coordination with 3 different escrow companies. Alex Jocovic handled everything professionally AND last but not least, the rates he offered beat the builder's finance company which had the builder's incentives!!!&#13;
Thanks Alex... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>29-07-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Outstanding! My wife and I have had many previous loans in the past. This by far was one of our best experiences. Alex Jocovic was wonderful, from first phone call to the end, he was with us every step of the way, not just sales. Our situation was complicated, with a 1031 exchange involved from a prior rental, a new home and all its confusion, sill Alex Jocovic was with us every day. We received status of the progress almost daily. So many coordination with 3 different escrow companies. Alex Jocovic handled everything professionally AND last but not least, the rates he offered beat the builder's finance company which had the builder's incentives!!!&#13;
Thanks Alex... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>22-03-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Easy and smooth process&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>02-04-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Great experience! Andrea helped me get a mortgage for my condo in Irvine. I compared a few lenders but her customer service made all the difference. I would definitely recommend her to anyone looking for a loan.  &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-04-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I can't say enough great things about my loan officer, Alex Jocovic at Pacific Beneficial Mortgage Company.  From start to finish, he was by my side with daily check-ins and phone calls, dealing with problems as they arose and handling a lot of the issues that came up along the way.  It was great knowing that someone had my back and offered great advice along the way.  A home purchase is such a stressful and scary experience but I felt confident knowing that I was in great hands with Alex.  You can't go wrong! ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>27-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I can't say enough great things about my loan officer, Alex Jocovic at Pacific Beneficial Mortgage Company.  From start to finish, he was by my side with daily check-ins and phone calls, dealing with problems as they arose and handling a lot of the issues that came up along the way.  It was great knowing that someone had my back and offered great advice along the way.  A home purchase is such a stressful and scary experience but I felt confident knowing that I was in great hands with Alex.  You can't go wrong! ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
very professional, kept us up-to-date with the progress of our loan, very accommodating&#13;
&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-12-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
excellent service. always called and emailed to give status of our loan. very accommodating.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>22-09-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I felt comfortable working with Alex. Alex was always patient in answering my questions and promptly returned my calls and emails. Even my Realtor commented on how pleasant it was to work with Alex. She asked me where did you find him at? &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>02-04-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I was a little skeptical about using a broker that i was not familiar with(not referred by anyone i know, ) but just by reading the Yelp reviews about Alex Jocovic i decided to gove him and Pacific Beneficial a try. I am very pleased and satisfied with the entire process! Alex Jocovic was very patient and always promptly returned my calls amd emails. I felt very comfortable and assured that we would close on time. Even my realtor commented on how easy it was to work with Alex... i would definitely recommend using Alex ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>23-06-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
During the whole process Alex was very attentive to every detail, always kept us informed and was available at all times whenever we had questions. Weve had many business dealings and services provided for us before but our experience with Alex was one of the most outsdanding ones weve ever had. We will without any hesitation recommend his services. Thank you!!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-12-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Everything worked great, a very smooth process. We are very pleased. Alex did an incredible job for us. Thank you!,&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>15-07-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
When we put an offer on in our home, our realtor (Susan Lyon in Napa) was not familiar with either Pacific Beneficial or Alex Jocovic and asked us if we were sure about using a mortgage company in Southern CA when we were up in the North. Then the selling realtor tried pushing us to use a local lender..&#13;
After our initial conversations with Alex we knew he was the broker we wanted to work with and my wife agreed so we refused to switch to a local lender and are very happy we did! Alex went above and beyond to get things done for us and was available both way before normal business hours on a morning and into the night as well, including on weekends. &#13;
As our purchase progressed, Susans caution changed to admiration as she complimented Alex and Pacific Beneficial to us on several occasions for their professionalism, responsiveness and commented on how easy they were making things for her on the loan side. In the end, we were in a position to close a full week early due to the hard work Alex and his team put in.&#13;
When it came to closing and sitting down to sign all of the necessary paperwork our escrow officer commented that This is a great rate, you must have a friend at the Mortgage Company?... Well, we didnt and, like our realtor we had not heard of Alex or Pacific Beneficial before our loan search however we now feel that we do have a friend at the mortgage company! &#13;
Thank You very much Alex and company; between you, you made a daunting task seem so easy and everything went through without a glitch from start to finish. We will certainly be recommending you to friends, as will our realtor, and we look forward to using your company for any future refinancing or home purchases in the future.&#13;
... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>08-06-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
When we put an offer on in our home, our realtor (Susan Lyon in Napa) was not familiar with either Pacific Beneficial or Alex Jocovic and asked us if we were sure about using a mortgage company in Southern CA when we were up in the North. Then the selling realtor tried pushing us to use a local lender..&#13;
After our initial conversations with Alex we knew he was the broker we wanted to work with and my wife agreed so we refused to switch to a local lender and are very happy we did! Alex went above and beyond to get things done for us and was available both way before normal business hours on a morning and into the night as well, including on weekends. &#13;
As our purchase progressed, Susans caution changed to admiration as she complimented Alex and Pacific Beneficial to us on several occasions for their professionalism, responsiveness and commented on how easy they were making things for her on the loan side. In the end, we were in a position to close a full week early due to the hard work Alex and his team put in.&#13;
When it came to closing and sitting down to sign all of the necessary paperwork our escrow officer commented that This is a great rate, you must have a friend at the Mortgage Company?... Well, we didnt and, like our realtor we had not heard of Alex or Pacific Beneficial before our loan search however we now feel that we do have a friend at the mortgage company! &#13;
Thank You very much Alex and company; between you, you made a daunting task seem so easy and everything went through without a glitch from start to finish. We will certainly be recommending you to friends, as will our realtor, and we look forward to using your company for any future refinancing or home purchases in the future.&#13;
... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>01-01-2018</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
June was extremely attentive and responsive throughout the process. In addition she was very courteous and a pleasure to work with.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>14-03-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Jason straightforward and extremely attentive throughout the process.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>14-03-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Jason Bean and June Lee were honest and very responsive. &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
It was a pleasure working with Alex. I was unfortunate with having to go through two failed escrows due to the conditions of the houses that I was in contract with, but Alex was patient and helped me through all three of my escrows until I finally closed on a house. If you are looking for a loan officer that is responsive and personable go with Alex. He will follow up with you consistently and make sure that you close on time. Overall I had an excellent experience working with Alex and Pacific Beneficial Mortgage... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>19-03-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
It was a pleasure working with Alex Jocovic. I was unfortunate with having to go through two failed escrows due to the conditions of the houses that I was in contract with, but Alex was patient and helped me through all three of my escrows until I finally closed on a house. If you are looking for a loan officer that is responsive and personable go with Alex. He will follow up with you consistently and make sure that you close on time. Overall I had an excellent experience working with Alex and Pacific Beneficial Mortgage... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Great for first time home buyers!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>13-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Kirk was very accommodating to me and my sisters. This is our very first home purchase. We were able to close Escrow just in time before our leasing contract is up for our previous apartment. Every questions that we have was mostly answered to our satisfaction even though it becomes repetitive at times. All in all, my family had a great experience working with Kirk. I highly recommend him to all first time home buyers for a much smoother and faster process. Also, he provides great customer service... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>26-10-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I am writing this review to share what ended up being an unpleasant experience with Kirk Gay and Pacific Beneficial Mortgage to other potential customers. &#13;
&#13;
I am a first time homebuyer and was originally going to go with a local mortgage broker for my loan, but wanted to shop around for a potential better rate, so I used LendingTree which is how Kirk contacted me. My original lender had offered to pay for my home appraisal in writing, and, wanting to compete, Kirk said he would pay for the appraisal (which he stated in writing) and asked for the letter the other lender had provided so he could get permission to have Pacific Beneficial pay for my appraisal. Kirk confirmed I would not be paying for the appraisal and was very happy with what Kirk was doing to accommodate me as a customer. However, when I closed on the home, the cost of the appraisal was on my Final Buyers Statement ($525). As Kirk had said that I would not be paying for the appraisal, I thought I would be reimbursed. I reached out to Kirk via email after close and got no further response than We paid for appraisal upfront but we get reimbursed. I then reached out to Kirk two times via email with no response. I then called the office and spoke to Kirks boss admin who instructed me to reach out to Kirks boss, Adam Carrion, which I did. It was only then that I received an email response from Kirk stating that the lender credit I received, which was less than the appraisal, was all I would receive to cover the cost, despite the fact that when I was entering into the loan Kirk told me that Pacific Beneficial would be paying for the appraisal and I would be receiving a lender credit. Kirk asked me to call him, which I did and left a voicemail, and he never called me back. I called Kirk again leaving a voicemail with no response. I then began reaching out to his boss Adam Carrion via email to continue to explain the situation. Only then did I receive an email from Kirk asking me to call him, which I did, left a voicemail, and received no response. I then called Adam and spoke to him on the phone and only then did I receive a call from Kirk, offering me a nominal amount of money. I stated that I wanted to be reimbursed for the entire appraisal amount and he said he would go back to the powers that be to see what he could do. I never heard from him. I reached out to Kirk and Adam via email to check in on status with no response. The next day I reached out again, voicing my displeasure and that I was going to take action via reviews. It was only then that I received an email from Kirk accusing me of extorting him. I want other potential customers to know about what occurred as not only was I misled, but I was treated terribly as a customer once Kirk had been paid his commission. It is extremely disappointing that this brokerage would go to these lengths over $525 after the fact when they promised this a customer.&#13;
... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>10-11-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Worked with Jason &amp; June &amp; it couldnt have been an easier process. Completely happy with my experience &amp; the process just depends how fast you respond to their requests. This was a refinance &amp; it was completed &amp; funded within under a month.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>11-10-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Worked with Jason &amp; June &amp; it couldnt have been an easier process. Completely happy with my experience &amp; the process just depends how fast you respond to their requests. This was a refinance &amp; it was completed &amp; funded within under a month. June was very helpful &amp; Im an Accountant with lots of questions &amp; she was very patient with me. Id ask for different terms &amp; loan amounts &amp; she was quick to give me the updated rates. She definitely has amazing customer service skills &amp; knowledge. I highly recommend... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-04-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Everything I said about my loan officer holds true for the company he works for.  The support staff, specifically Summer Anderson was as thorough and efficient as Rowel and as accommodating and informative.  In this day and age of doing business without ever meeting the people helping you - you have to be an expert in sizing up people and their product in just a few conversations or you could be fortunate enough to find Pacific Mortgage.  Honestly, met or exceeded all of their competitors and all of my expectations!!!... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>12-09-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Absolutely the best experience I have ever had dealing with a loan officer - or any other loan related endeavor for that matter.  Rowel was friendly, knowledgeable, patient and extraordinarily helpful in choosing the right loan for me.  I got precisely what was promised in RECORD time and Rowel was available and eager to answer ALL of my questions every step of the way.  Not only will I recommend him to anyone and everyone I can, I will call him when I need anything related to my loan in the future... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>25-11-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Provided very timely and friendly service to bring my loan to a close quickly &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>21-08-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Friendly and efficient.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
They were quick, professional, friendly, and cost effective.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>07-10-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
It was a pleasure to work with Pacific Beneficial on our refinance. We worked with Rowel Enriquez and he was incredibly responsive any time we had questions or encountered issues.&#13;
&#13;
I would definitely recommend Pacific Beneficial and gladly call on them services in the future.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>28-04-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
It was a pleasure to work with Rowel on our refinance. He was incredibly responsive any time we had questions or encountered issues.&#13;
&#13;
I would definitely recommend him and gladly ask for his services in the future.&#13;
&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>14-02-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Had slight difficulty with online documents and signing&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>19-03-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Accommodating, easy to work with, good products&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>25-11-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
My loan officer was a really big help. He was very patient, and helped me save some money on the closing cost. Thanks again, I would definitely refer to a friend.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>28-11-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
It was the first time we refinanced our home and Kirk was Knowledgeable and made it very easy for us throughout the process. Great rate and service. Thank you.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>30-06-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Our contact Maurice was professional and courteous in all of our discussions. He explained the details and worked to meet our timelines. He was excellent.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-04-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Overall a very fine job. No cost to me, and I received the prevailing rate. A few minor paperwork mistakes which required some repeated forms to be signed, but nothing worth worrying over. Peter did a very good job.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>14-03-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Probably this was a more challenging refinance. Alex Zelada worked very had on this!&#13;
But despite numerous assurances of getting close to the finish line, it took over 3 months , and the 45 day rate lock had to be extended.&#13;
Most of the problem seemed to be with Quicken. Requests for documents was piecemeal, and each new request caused a delay; this most likely due to Quicken, and Q did put everything in a holding pattern, apparently without the brokers' knowledge. It was discovered only after my following up to see what the delay was .&#13;
Also there were a few instances of PB staff not fully reading thru correspondence and making assumptions that weren't entirely accurate and could have been significant to the borrower.&#13;
&#13;
If doing it over I would go with a local broker with a comparable rate... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>08-01-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I am writing this review to share what ended up being an unpleasant experience with Kirk Gay and Pacific Beneficial Mortgage to other potential customers. &#13;
&#13;
I am a first time homebuyer and was originally going to go with a local mortgage broker for my loan, but wanted to shop around for a potential better rate, so I used LendingTree which is how Kirk contacted me. My original lender had offered to pay for my home appraisal in writing, and, wanting to compete, Kirk said he would pay for the appraisal (which he stated in writing) and asked for the letter the other lender had provided so he could get permission to have Pacific Beneficial pay for my appraisal. Kirk confirmed I would not be paying for the appraisal and was very happy with what Kirk was doing to accommodate me as a customer. However, when I closed on the home, the cost of the appraisal was on my Final Buyers Statement ($525). As Kirk had said that I would not be paying for the appraisal, I thought I would be reimbursed. I reached out to Kirk via email after close and got no further response than We paid for appraisal upfront but we get reimbursed. I then reached out to Kirk two times via email with no response. I then called the office and spoke to Kirks boss admin who instructed me to reach out to Kirks boss, Adam Carrion, which I did. It was only then that I received an email response from Kirk stating that the lender credit I received, which was less than the appraisal, was all I would receive to cover the cost, despite the fact that when I was entering into the loan Kirk told me that Pacific Beneficial would be paying for the appraisal and I would be receiving a lender credit. Kirk asked me to call him, which I did and left a voicemail, and he never called me back. I called Kirk again leaving a voicemail with no response. I then began reaching out to his boss Adam Carrion via email to continue to explain the situation. Only then did I receive an email from Kirk asking me to call him, which I did, left a voicemail, and received no response. I then called Adam and spoke to him on the phone and only then did I receive a call from Kirk, offering me a nominal amount of money. I stated that I wanted to be reimbursed for the entire appraisal amount and he said he would go back to the powers that be to see what he could do. I never heard from him. I reached out to Kirk and Adam via email to check in on status with no response. The next day I reached out again, voicing my displeasure and that I was going to take action via reviews. It was only then that I received an email from Kirk accusing me of extorting him. I want other potential customers to know about what occurred as not only was I misled, but I was treated terribly as a customer once Kirk had been paid his commission. It is extremely disappointing that this brokerage would go to these lengths over $525 after the fact when they promised this a customer.&#13;
... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>13-08-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
The intake rep was very nice but the loan officer seemed annoyed by my inquiries for clarification. That's too bad, all other reviews on the website were very positive on customer service. I do hope somebody reviews the phone call. Didn't get past the initial conversation. To be fair, this review system required a rating for Rate, Fees, &amp; Responsiveness, I was required to pick a category and I selected "poor" but I honestly don't have an opinion on the matter, my preference would have been to leave these blank... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>06-02-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I applied to three different lenders and the other two came across as organized, responsive and caring. After my application was filed and the rate was locked, they sent me an application to review which had many errors and then it took them over forever to make corrections. I emailed and called to inquire about the status of my loan and it took nearly a week to get a reply. I emailed again later to ask when an appraisal would be ordered, and almost another week went by before I got a reply. Poor communication with customers .Even though I applied with another lender the very same week I applied with Pacific, I was asked to sign docs with that other lender before an appraisal was even ordered by Pacific!! Very frustrating. Cannot recommend them... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>04-01-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
This company responded to my Lending Tree application, and I picked them out to work with because their initial e-mails were polite and professional. I spoke with a broker Adam and explained my somewhat complicated situation. He advised me to send financial documents (including 1040s, W2s, etc) so his folks could make a preliminary decision before I started an applicaiton. I immediately sent him all the HIGHLY personal paperwork he requested. A few days later he e-mailed once saying "everything looks good but we need to be sure", and after that, he never e-mailed, called, or notified me via mental telepathy. I e-mailed requesting an update, but NOTHING.... ARGHHH... Why did you waste my time? If your company couldn't help me, no biggie, just tell me! But getting NO update from these folks really makes me paranoid about having shared all of my financial info with them. Note to Lending Tree, drop this company!!! Note to applicants: there are plenty of good companies out there, so steer clear of this one... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>negative</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>04-09-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I worked with Kory and Carla at NASB. They were a superb team and provided excellent, responsive and knowledgeable service throughout the entire process. Ours was a complicated process with a refinance and a loan and they hung in there with us the entire time. It was a great experience working with both of them. I highly recommend them and will use them in the future for all of my mortgage needs... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>19-03-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Kory was by far the best loan officer I have ever worked with. We were dealing with a complicated refinance and purchase of two different properties and he was cool, calm, professional and extremely knowledgeable throughout the entire process. I wouldnt use anyone else moving forward. His level of integrity and responsiveness is second to none. Thanks for everything, Kory... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>10-02-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Expert loan officer, well versed in VA and the financial impacts of loan component changes. The best I have worked with across 7 home buying/selling deals.  Now advocated for by the #1 real estate broker in the state due to his ability to close complicated and high pressure deals.  She places him at the top of the list after 32 years in the business!  &#13;
&#13;
Professionally and patiently answers detailed questions and can rally the expanded NASB team (also stellar!) to support your needs.  He handled my complicated VA loan that seemed to change every week while we tried to buy an Antebellum home (tough comps) during my retirement from the military (tough income verification) with five families all swapping homes (tons of contingencies).  Everything along the way mattered and Aaron and the NASB team got it done (even on weekends) and closed on time with the best interest rate in the market and no added origination fees.  &#13;
&#13;
Look, do NOT pass up an opportunity to work with him. ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>12-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
The NASB team went above and beyond for me and my family and closed an important VA home loan on time despite many changes, my military retirement, and a very challenging Antebellum home that required the entire NASB team to pull out all the stops, know the rules and regulations, and guide us through a tough VA process.  I truly believe we would not have closed on time with a different team.  I will only recommend NASB for home loans...especially complicate VA loans... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>02-02-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Dallas Goodlet and his entire team are deserving a special thank you.  He was as professional as they come and closed our loan in 12 days.  We were with another competitor originally and he called, saving us thousands over our current lender. It was a real pleasure getting to work with this institution and a class act like Dallas.  Great job!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>27-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Comments:	To begin my wife and I were at the point of signing completion with the leader of online home mortgage service. We were not satisfied with the origination cost so we applied to lending tree for competitive bids. Several lender matched or slightly beat NASB but none were convincing at closing on time. We chose NASB because of Dallas Goodlet believability on the closing. The sales, loan service and application process was competitive, assuring, professional, timely, supportive, and truthful. Dallas Goodlet/ Brent Custer and the whole NASB team delivered the mortgage on time and at the price promised. We are completely satisfied and appreciative of the staff, product and service of your company. Kudos to all ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>28-11-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Working with Jon was such an amazing experience! From the start he offered answers to any questions I had since after all this was our first home purchase! Jon was always a phone call away ready to help where needed. He made the stringent home buying process as easy as possible! I would definitely recommend any potential buyers to work with Jon, I know for myself I will be calling him if we ever decide to buy another house!&#13;
&#13;
Thanks Jon... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
NASB was amazing to work with! The pre-approval process was easy and informational. We chose our home and closed within 30 days of our agreement date! Thanks NASB for making our first home purchase an amazing experience!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-02-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
&#13;
Jon Barrett was a great asset to my husband and I. He made our mortgage loan process extremely simple and quick! Jon was knowledgeable, helpful, patient and accurate. We would suggest anyone shopping for a mortgage loan to give Jon a call.&#13;
&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>28-11-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Jon Barrett was a great asset to my husband and I. He made our mortgage loan process extremely simple and quick! Jon was knowledgeable, helpful, patient and accurate. We will be passing Jon's name along to anyone looking for a mortgage loan!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I can't express how incredibly awesome our experience was with working with Bryant Small at NASB. As a military family, we have purchased or refinanced many homes and this was by far the BEST experience we have ever had. Bryant makes it easy and took the time to discuss the best options for us. I've never met Bryant, but you can't mistake authenticity and we knew instantly he and NASB were who we were going with.... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>17-02-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Best loan officer I could have hoped for! Jeff exceeded my expectations. He worked very hard to get me the best rate possible. Highly recommended &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>04-03-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Adam was great to work with during our refi!  His attention to detail made this a smooth and easy transaction.   It has been several years since we've gone thru the home loan process and we were unsure where to start.   After talking with Adam, we were confident he was the one to help us with our refi.  He was professional, helpful, very knowledgeable about the loan process and answered all of our questions in a timely manner.   I would highly recommend Adam and would not hesitate to work with him again... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>09-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Great website, knowledgeable, responsive and always got back to us quickly with answers to our questions.  Mortgage process can be very tedious and they made it easy.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-04-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
We received offers from multiple banks after our lending tree request for a mortgage.  Alex Madewell from NASB was by far the best offer.  He made the entire process easy and was very knowledgeable.  The closing on this home was seamless, no surprises.  I would definitely recommend Alex Madewell and NASB to anyone looking for a mortgage.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>10-04-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Rob was very helpful in getting this loan closed. Few issues on our end we didn't know about but he was still able to get it done on time.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>18-01-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Peter and his team were great to work with. They were professional and prompt with their responses. They answered all my questions and somehow got us to closing on time despite various roadblocks we encountered.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Adam came highly recommended and from the first time we spoke with him, it was clear why.  He was friendly, professional, knowledgeable, and worked hard to ensure we were taken care of in all aspects.  Beyond the necessary effective communication skills, he brought a personal touch after we closed by sending us a hand written note of congratulations.  I will recommend him to everyone I know buying a house.... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>12-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
A real stand up guy. From the beginning Mr. Barrett alievatied any uncertainties we faced with buying our first home. This guidance and expertise was certainly what a first time homebuyer would hope for. From beginning to the very end he stood by us and walked us through the entire process. Even down to the wire at closing Mr. Barrett stepped up and saved us thousands by identifying an errounous mistake in the contract. When I buy again, Ill call Jon. Thank you Jon Barrett! We certainly enjoyed working with you... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>12-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I had the pleasure of working with Mr. Barrett from NASB and I couldnt be more please. From the very beginning Mr. Barrett guided us on our journey with the upmost courtesy and respect. Even while closing Mr. Barrett once again came to the rescue helping me save even more money! A big thanks to Mr. Barrett and the team at NASB. When I buy again I know who Ill call&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>11-06-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
As a first time homebuyer I was walking blindly, Bryant became my guide! I recall telling him "I don't speak mortgage" and that was no problem at all. Bryant was kind, understanding, and genuinely cared throughout the entire process from my online application to the day we became homeowners. He was very prompt and always gave clear explanations of what was happening, next steps, and what path would be in my best interest. Even when there were bumps in the road he was there to smooth them out. I would recommend Bryant to anyone seeking financial wisdom in their buying/refinancing process... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>12-05-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
They got me the best deal. They price matched and did even better. Fortunate I got to work with them. &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>04-09-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Alex was persistent, diligent, and thorough. He was easy to work with and got me an excellent rate on my home. Next time I buy Ill absoltely work with him. &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>26-01-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
My wife and I have purchased several homes over the years and have worked with a number of different mortgage companies. Our experience with Jeremy and Brent (Custer) has been, by far, the best we have ever experienced. If we are ever in the market again, we will definitely be back and will recommend NASB to anyone we know who is looking for a mortgage.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>11-06-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Great customer service. Always available when I called and very respectful. Thanks for working extra hard to close on time. &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>09-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I would like to thank Brent for working with us. He kept encouraging us when we felt we would get turned down because of a previous lender. Brent and his team did everything possible to meet our deadline. Thanks to him,  we are now happy home owners. &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>15-09-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I first inquired about a loan with Brent (6) months ago. I then told him I wanted to put it all on hold once I found out the cost to buy out my lease. After (6) months I contacted him in the morning and told him it was time for me to get serious. He responded within the hour and we were rolling again.&#13;
&#13;
2 weeks later I found a home I wanted to make an offer on. 4 weeks later I closed on the home. During that time I always knew what was going on. We talked daily. He made me feel comfortable through the whole process and I always felt like I was in control. Honestly, purchasing the home was much easier than I thought. I'd recommend him to anyone.... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>19-03-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
It had been ten years since I bought a house and I was little nervous of what I could afford this time around and going through the process again. Adam couldn't have been better to work with. He was great at communicating and making me feel at ease. He got us the best rate and was a dream to work with. He completely took the anxiety out of home buying. You will regret not using him. He is knowledgeable and you can tell he really cares about you... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Fred was very nice, and always available to address my concerns. He seems to really care about his customers. Going through a refinance is never very pleasant, but Fred did his best to make it as painless as possible. Thanks Fred!!&#13;
Best,&#13;
Kary&#13;
&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>13-04-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I worked with Kory Klossner, a loan officer with NASB.  After confirming he could offer a much lower rate than my financial institution, he then took the additional time to explain the pros and cons of different loan types (conventional versus VA loans).  Kory also took the time to calculate approximate monthly payments and closing costs for each.  I never felt like I was being pressured or rushed into a decision, in fact I felt quite the opposite.  He gave me whatever time I needed to fully understand my options and make the choice that was right for me, based upon my unique circumstances.  Kory went above and beyond to make me feel comfortable with what has been the biggest financial decision of my life.  Thanks Kory...5 stars... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-12-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I worked with Kory Klossner, a loan officer with NASB.  After confirming he could offer a much lower rate than my financial institution, he then took the additional time to explain the pros and cons of different loan types (conventional versus VA loans).  Kory also took the time to calculate approximate monthly payments and closing costs for each.  I never felt like I was being pressured or rushed into a decision, in fact I felt quite the opposite.  He gave me whatever time I needed to fully understand my options and make the choice that was right for me, based upon my unique circumstances.  Kory went above and beyond to make me feel comfortable with what has been the biggest financial decision of my life.  Thanks Kory...5 stars... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-08-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I couldn't have been more pleased with Aaron's customer service. My father recommended Aaron when I was looking to buy a house. Aaron fought to get me the best rate and made sure that everything went as planned. When I wasn't able to move my closing date up to keep my rate interest rate, Aaron told me not to worry about it and he would cover the cost difference. He did the same thing when we had to pay extra to rush the appraiser to close on time. I would and will recommend Aaron to anyone looking to buy a home because I know he will do a great job like he did for me.... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>16-08-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
I can't begin to express my happiness with working with Aaron, not only is he professional and knowledgeable but he literally ended up saving me thousands of dollars on my loan! I thought I had good rate until I spoke with him and we were able to lower it almost a full 1% which saved us hundreds of dollars per month and then he was able to get everything approved/closed on a very tight timeline of less than 4 weeks! I highly recommend him... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Very responsive and worked hard to get us approved.  The mortgage experience itself can be very stressful, but Jon really made us feel like someone was on our side.  Thanks again for everything.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-12-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Joey was very helpful. We appreciated his friendly manner and his timely responses.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>05-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Our loan officer, Joey Hartegan, was friendly and very helpful. My wife and I were very pleased that we chose NASB to refinance our home.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>09-12-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
My family and I shopped around for home mortgages for a while. We currently reside in New Jersey and every mortgage company wanted nearly 20k to close. I found North American Savings Bank online, and Steve was the person that I was assigned to work with. He was wonderful to say the least. Steve would always answer my calls and emails promptly. In addition, when out of the office, Steve always made sure a colleague assisted me. I honestly cannot say enough about (NASB). Ultimately, the were able to get me a much lower interest rate and monthly payment on my home. I highly recommend Steve to anyone ... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>02-08-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
RC was excellent to work with!  He is a straight shooter and an honorable fellow veteran. He ensured we understood what was happening, what to expect and how long it would take. I can't recommend anyone more for your lending needs when working with a VA loan, you need a loan officer who "knows" what they are doing. He is great at what he does and will personally ensure your closing is on time. Even with an extremely slow appraiser who did not meet deadlines causing delays, we still closed on time thanks to RC, his professionalism and his dedication to keep his word. His team is great to work with as well... Read More&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>27-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Very smooth experience.....working with a VA loan, closing on time, NASB was extremely easy to work with. As a veteran, you WANT a lender who understands and easily funds VA loans and NASB meets this requirement with five stars. Other lenders we have worked with in the past do not meet NASB's service, especially closing on time, in my experience. Recommend highly!&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>14-02-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Outstanding service and always timely&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>07-07-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Fred went above and beyond to make sure everything went smoothly including making calls while on vacation. Fred works hard to make your dreams come true.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>20-12-2016</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Fast, helpful, best service possible. I heartily recommend them to everyone.&#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
  <Feedback>
    <date>24-05-2017</date>
    <feedback_content>&#13;
Aaron did everything humanly possible to get me the best rate and terms that he possibly could.&#13;
&#13;
He listened to me and responded to my needs with concern, care, and expertise.&#13;
&#13;
I could never have anyone who could have helped me more by being a caring, knowledgable, patient, and responsive individual.&#13;
&#13;
Many thanks to Mr. Spring &#13;
        </feedback_content>
    <sentiment>positive</sentiment>
  </Feedback>
</Feedbacks>
